by H.
I'm scared of the deepest part.
LOL!
You should stop sneezing.
(laughs)
You're getting too much free material.
That's nice.
Actually, I thought you wanted to ride the trolley for the contest.
(laughter)
Hey, that guy is the worst.
ENDING.
Hi, I'm Tokyo Theiston. Please do me a favor.
Quickly, and please welcome Mr. Sakuma.
So, here they are today. Please come in.
Interesting, interesting, interesting. They are all funny.
If it's comedy, let us do it. Leave it to us.
Come on. Ruff Ruff.
Please do.
So, that's it. I look forward to working with you all today.
Let's do our best.
So, this time, we have a special guest.
Let me introduce him.
Let me introduce him. This is our guest. Please come in.
Yes, please give him a hand.
Please do.
There it is, there it is, there it is.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry. Once again, our special guest is Mr. Buttigie Ujihara. Please do.
Please give him my best regards.
Ujihara-san, Buttigire Ujihara-san, do you know everybody?
What?
Everybody knows him.
What? Mr. Hayase, really? You love it?
My friend likes rap music, and he makes me watch rap videos every day at lunchtime.
He makes me watch them.
I mean, I rap, but it's not my main thing.
I don't do anything like that.
I thought it was something like TikTok or YouTube.
Yes, yes, yes. Ujihara-san is a TikTok and YouTube distributor, and he gets pissed off at all the comments he receives on his live broadcasts.
He is active on TikTok and YouTube, and he is always pissed off at all the comments that come in to his live streaming.
Last year, he won the world's largest amount of spacha.
Ehhhh....
Is that so?
You don't snap at all, do you?
This is my only, I don't know, strength.
Wait, you're the best in the world?
Well, I'm unofficially the world's largest spatter amount per day.
Can you say how much?
I won't say how much. I won't tell you.
I won't tell you. I won't tell you at all.
So, if you can return the money instantly, it will be useful everywhere.
That's right. Instantaneous power.
Yes, Fujisaki.
I had some kind of class change.
I can't make friends at all.
Ah.
Hmmm...
I don't think you'll snap out of it that quickly.
In response to your worries...
But there's something else, something like that...
Yes, Natsume.
My bangs and eyelashes are not looking good lately.
This is a big problem.
Yes, yes, my bangs and eyelashes are in bad shape, what should I do?
I don't know what to do!
I've never cared about my
That's great!
Yes, Saito.
I've been having nindin-siri-shiri at dinner about 4 times a week.
Nindin siri-siri.
Does that mean your mother makes it?
Yes, I'm getting tired of it.
That's a miracle, but my parents are like that, so give up.
I can't.
They've been serving me corn for a week.
Corn?
I kept getting corn on the cob.
I don't mean corn like it's doing something.
It's just that the corn just kept coming out, like really, really something.The corn really came out something all the time.
What's with that dish?
Someday your parents will get tired of it.
I'll wait there.
Yes, Yoshimura.
I've been getting a lot of height teasing from the younger members lately.
How can I avoid being taken advantage of?
First of all, I'd like to say to the kid who made a comment about my height...
It's time to stop this kind of teasing.
Please say something that stings.
There's a serious side to it, too.
Let's get to the project this time!
Follow in the footsteps of Ujihara, the world's best spacha!
Let's follow Ujihara, the world's best spacha player, and get pissed off at a pretty picture!
The rules are simple.
Various cute pictures will be shown on the monitor.
All you have to do is to get mad at them.
Did you get the gist?
It's hard.
That's all there is to it.
I thought it was hard, too.
It's hard.
This project is hard?
I just lose my temper, that's all.
Well, here we go... the first one is here.
Now, let's see... you're a great cat, Fujisaki! Don't flirt with me, you cat!
Yay! His face is so beautiful.
Fujisaki's face is the best in the world.
Let's keep going. It's like a magnet stuck to a flower.
Is that sharp? No, it's not.
Well, it's funny, but it's sharp. It's like he's doing a one-liner.
Takanashi, that's where they put the fruit.
But it's nice. I like your angle.
Let's get to work!
The simulation's getting weird.
321, please.
Don't slurp on that stinky mouth of yours.
I don't know if my mouth stinks or not.
I'd like to see a little more of that overall sharpness.
Is the voltage of the sharpness a little shallow?
I'd like to see him really pissed off, even if it's only in the extreme.
Wait a minute, it's not sharp enough.
Sasaki, can you do it?
It's not sharp enough.
I'm just using it as an example.
Hayashi, can you?
Let's go. Hayashi, please.
I'm a dog person.
I like the angle, too.
Nagamatsu, can you?
Don't rub your nose on it. You'll get snot on it.
It makes me feel like home.
That's good.
Yoshimura.
Yes, Yoshimura.
This one is prettier.
Wonderful.
What about this?
I'm just competing with you.
It's not real, is it? No?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I said no.
I just thought it might be a good idea.
Then you guys do it. I'll do it.
That's me.
As an idol, I liked it.
But not according to Fujiwara's rules.
I guess I'm a little short on the "butthole".
I really want his eyes to be sharp.
Eyes are important, too.
I'll make the first one.
Eyes busted up!
What do you think?
It's scary at the back.
That's...
That's a different kind of smash and grab.
Not the kind where they're all cut to pieces.
Then, Mr. Fujiwara...
Yes, yes.Yes, yes, yes.
Metaphone?
I'll take this cat, please.
You shouldn't have blocked up his nose.
He's out of order.
It's a real one.
It's a little... cut when it's old.
You shouldn't block his nose.
It's a bad idea to block the nose.
Let's go around to the next picture.
Here's the next one.
Yes, a seal.
The seal is smiling a little bit.
Don't be happier than I am.
Oh, wow! Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
Did you find it?
It's good to see some background.
The background?
Here you go, Saito.
You have a very small proportion of face.
Ha-ha-ha.
You swear.
Nice outfit, bad mouth.
Nice. That's settled.
Come on, Natsume.
Don't you sneeze. It's white.
That's nice.
And you've got a nice voice.
That was great.
So we can all stand up and say it.
Yeah, basically, when you're pissed.
You're losing control.
I see.
We can't just sit there, can we?
Let's go, Takanashi.
All right.
You're getting too much free material.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
That's great.
Let's get to it.
Changmatsu.
What's so funny?
Wow.
I wanted to get the batch out.
I wanted to.
That's great.
Come on, Fujisaki.
It's too white to see.
Maybe they're not the same.
Beautiful is good.
I see.
The way you find the point.
Come on, Sasaki.
Ready?
Let's stand up.
Stand up.
Let's cut to the chase.
Speak up.
I don't know.
Isn't this one good, too?
It's real.
Yeah, it's real.
It's real. It's the right thing to do.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hey, there's a shark coming up behind you.
Gentle, gentle chi.
Caution. Still caution.
No, but it's an emergency.
Oh, it's already coming. It's already coming.
I liked the way you said that.
As for the seventh variation.
Nice miso soup.
Come on, Hibino, let's go for it.
What's with the yankee pose and everything?
Where the hell did your ears go?
I like the way you're sitting.
Like a ball boy.Like a ball boy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Tennis.
Like sitting with the ball boy.
Okay, excuse me, Mr. Ujiyama.
I have to do it after this.
I've been thinking about it.
I'm a comedian too.
I'm sure this will be tough for you.
I've been nervous since this morning.
What?
You're doing your best to choose now.
I understand how you feel.
I don't really want to read the ballot.
But I'm a professional.
I'm a professional.
Mr. Ujiyama, please take this picture.
If you don't say anything...
I'd screw up like this. Wait a minute.
You guys, put on a pretty face.
When the flower garden is playing, the music will start.
Put on a pretty face.
It's all right, sir.
I'm just doing a little mental work here right now.
Yes, thank you.
Mr. Uchihara, please.
Shut up and say something.
That's great.
I was just about to cut this off. Oh, Fujisaki.
Wow, you're fast.
I'm a loner.
You compare yourself so often.
No, no, no. It's all about the feelings. That's important, too.
That's important. Let's go.
Okay, Natsume.
Shut up and eat the food.
Scary. Scary. Nice.
Okay, Takanashi.
Lightning's coming. Are you okay?
Gobi? Gobi?
Are you okay? You don't see a lot of people listening.
You must be Mr. Hananokihara.
Mr. Hananokihara.
Here you go.
You guys should go back to the zoo!
Don't you talk about people properly.
That's okay. I'm doing it for you guys.
I don't care what you're doing.
Just go home.
Hey, Changmatsu!
Just a little drink for the rabbit! You poor thing!
That's good.
It's nice.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
That's great.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, Hayashi.
You guys should really look at flowers!
Don't you agree?
It's hard to look at flowers.
Come on, come on, come on, come on. Yes.
Fuji hollyhock, three days.
You guys can't eat them all!
Oh!
I was outraged.
Fuji-Aoi, Natsume...
I'm scared of those two in the back row!
Even if we try to get them back...
I'll try to get it back.
Great.
Let's go, Kusaki!
Yes, let's go.
If you don't like four dumplings...
Let's go to Hibino. Can we go? Yes, let's go.
I hope you guys are taking your garbage home with you.
That's great.
That's good... That's good...
Come on, Yoshimura.
Yes, sir.
He was probably in the mess just now.
Huh?
This is so gross.This is already egregious.
I'll be back to messing with the temporary dye soon.
Sad dream.
Oh, man.
Okay, so we all did it one at a time.
You guys were great.
I'm just a senior, so...
No, no, no, of course not. I'm just a pissed-off Uzue, so don't worry about it.
You should stand up, too.
I should stand up too.
I'd better put some energy into it.
I just wanted to say something to the bear.
Hey, bear...
Did you wash your hands?
No, I haven't.
Sure, I'll eat my onigiri naked.
Next game...
I'm an MC.
You're all carbs. You'll get hard!
Muscle... muscle.
That's nice.
What's next, Takeru?
That's really not even agar.
Takeru.
Takeru... he's the hardest worker.
He's got a temper.
Hey, hey, hey!
Melon soda's bad for you!
Oh, it's no good!
Hey, this ain't good!
Yeah, it's not good.
Don't laugh at me when I say this.
This is a definite no-no.
It's a no-no for a guy not to smile.
Here's the next picture.
Oh, so that's how it is.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, that's it.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like you all to go crazy over this picture.
I'm 22 years old.
Graduated from college
Me in my first year as an AD.
AD.
I just talked to the staff, and it seems like they're putting this out there without asking for confirmation.
Yeah, well, I'm surprised too, but it's okay.
Now then, let's see if you're all mad about this.
Let's go, Mr. Fujisaki.
Go ahead.
Your hair hasn't changed.
I see... in response to this.
It's the same as it used to be.
I've always been with you.
Parted down the middle.
Let's go.
Yoshimura.
He's getting his color back.
What? What?
You said Corocoro Comic.
You just said CoroCoro Comics.
I read CoroCoro Comics recently.
That's great.
Okay, Takanashi.
You've been producing idols for 20 years, so be prepared.
Great.
Yeah, that's why I said you'll be busy.
That's great.
Next, Natsume.
I'm scared of you, Natsume.
Don't act like you're the coolest guy I've ever met.
This is the old Mr. Sakuma. Are you mad now?
No, back then, I still had this... how should I put it...
I wanted to make a funny show, and I wanted to be popular.
Still there?
Do you still want to be popular?
There was a little bit of that.
It's an eyesore.
Here you go, Saito.Come on, Saito.
Don't start thinking like a performer.
That's right.
Oh, shit, I'm losing it.
I'm coming in!
I'm going in!
I'm gonna tell the producers to stop!
Turn it into an Internet news story.
Sakuma, I'm in.
I'm going in. I'm going in.
I'm going in.
He's a bad guy.
The worst of the worst.
But that's okay, let's go on and on!
Chomatsu
Let's go, please!
I've been wanting to ride the trolley since this very moment.
Wait a minute. He's the worst.
He's doing a double-take, isn't he?
He's double-crossing me. I'm in denial.
No, no, no. I went with both.
We both went.
That's great.
Come on, Hibino, can you do it?
You know, you can say whatever you want to say to Mr. Sakuma.
You know, just let it out.
Let's go. Hibino, please.
Thanks for thinking of us when you're so busy.
That's nice.
I'm touched.
I'm glad you liked it, Dad.
But it's good.
Come on, come on, come on.
Sasaki, can you do it?
Let's go for it.
You're a producer and you're out of control!
Great! Now it's so good!
That was so good!
No, I liked the way you just said that.
That wasn't me snapping at you, that was Delftan snapping at me.
I see. That's what happened.
Well, then, let me give you an example of fear.
But, excuse me, I think this came out rather quickly.
Don't look at me, idiot!
I see.
It's coming out this way, that's for sure.
You want to play? You want to play? Yes, sir.
It's on the carpet.
You want to play?
Don't look like you've had all the laughs since then!
I'm not in the position where I'm doing all the laughs.
You're like a god of comedy.
Comedy god.
So...
What's with the closing without Takeru?
I'm screwed!
I'm out of control!
What the hell, Takeru's, it didn't work earlier.
Even if I do Takeru's, he won't thank me anyway, so I'll just close it out.
But did I do Takeru's earlier?
Hey, hey, hey, I'm gonna cry!
I'm gonna cry!
Well, Mr. Ujiyama, before I announce the "Bad Points"...
Please announce the "Best of Butt-heads"!
First of all, I would like to say that I liked this one by this person.
But first of all, I'd have to say Mr. Fujisaki's eyes.
I think it's more his face than his lines.
Now, Mr. Ujiyama, lastly, the "no" points.
The best of butsugiri was not so good, it was too weak...
Who will add more no-no points?
Oh, "bad points"?
I'll just read it as it is... "Dame Point Takeru.
Hey!
That's not Mr. Fujiwara's opinion!
Prime Minister Spass.
And I'm two points ahead of everyone else.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, I could be in trouble.
But Takeru, I didn't do anything today.
Don't say that!
You're missing so much!
You there, who just finished watching the video.You've finished watching the video, there you are.
I'm glad you watched it all the way through.
How was it? Did you enjoy it?
Wait a minute, you didn't subscribe to our channel?
I can't believe it!
Hit the subscribe button. I'll subscribe in a second!
Come on, Monomin!
You'll be hypnotized into subscribing!
Thank you, you hit the subscribe button!
Thank you for subscribing!